[Music]
Location may require putaway, warehouse
receipt, or both when dealing with
purchase processes. This update enables
use of warehouse processes for project
related
purchases. It allows you to create
purchase orders for locations where
directed putaway and pick is enabled.
for other locations. It allows you to
use standard standardized processes when
dealing with purchase
orders. Let's see the demo. Let's open
project planning lines. We use the same
item in all lines, but locations are
different as we want to explore impact
of various warehouse
settings. The silver location requires
put
away. The yellow location only requires
a warehouse receipt. The white location
has the directed putaway and pick
setting enabled means this location
requires both receipt and putaway
steps. The main location doesn't require
any special warehouse handling of
inbound
transactions. First, we create purchase
order for required items using the new
functionality added in the previous
release. We will create one purchase
order covering all needed items. Next,
we generate an inventory put away for
the silver
location. Now, open and post the created
document to receive
item. We then create warehouse receipts.
One for the yellow location receipt
only, one for the white location,
directed putaway, and pick. When
purchase order is linked to project, the
putaway step will be skipped since items
are consumed immediately. Finally, we
receive the item at the main location
directly from the purchase order. We
also post the invoice. Purchase order is
completely
posted. So, we are returning to project
planning lines where you can see that
quantity and cost is already
registered. Thank you for watching. You
can find more information about
capability in the release note. You can
find the link in the description.